

BIRTHDATE -----

28/07/1992

NATIONALITY

Italian

CONTACTS

andreagulino@me.com

+39-3451462332

PROGRAMMING SKILLS -----

JAVATYPESCRIPTCI/CDAWSDYNAMODBλCLOUDFORMATION NEXTJSMONITORINGANALYTICSBIG DATAAPACHE SPARKPYTHONSCALAGIT

WAYS OF WORKING

AGILE LeSS TDD

WEBSITE

andreagulino.github.io

ANDREA GULINO

PHD IN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY

Summary -----

I am a PhD in Information Technology, specialized in the design of scalable systems and algorithms for data-intensive applications.

.....

Since March 2021 I have been working as a software engineer on the re-design and development of a WW **E-commerce** platform along with the integration of new payment systems.

Work Experience

GUCCI

Digital Product Developer

2021-present

- · New e-commerce platform design and full-stack development
- · Integration of new payment systems

Politecnico di Milano

2018-2019

Teaching Assistant

Basic and advanced programming classes for engineering students

Education -----

Politecnico di Milano

2017-2020	PhD cum laude in Information Technology
2014-2017	Master's Degree in Computer Science and Engineering 110 cum laude
2011-2014	Bachelor's Degree - Ingegneria Informatica

Tongji University 同济大学 - Shanghai

2012-2013 Double degree exchange program (1 year)

Research

Research Areas

Cloud Computing, System Architectures, Distributed Algorithms, Databases, Computational Genomics.

Oral Presentations

2018 IEEE Big Data (Seattle), 2019 IEEE BIBM (San Diego), 2020 IEEE MASCOTS (Nice).

Publications

14 publications, 7 as a first author. More details are available on my personal website and on <u>Google Scholar</u>.

Collaborations

Oxford University, Banca D'Italia.